const data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "The longest river in the world is the:",
      incorrectAnswers: [                                                                                                                                                                                                    "Amazon River", "Yangtze River", "Mississippi River"],
      correctAnswer: "Nile River",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "The capital of France is:",
      incorrectAnswers: ["London", "Berlin",  "Madrid"],
      correctAnswer: "Paris",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "The Great Barrier Reef is located off the coast of:",
      incorrectAnswers: [ "Brazil", "Mexico", "Canada"],
      correctAnswer: "Australia",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "The highest mountain peak in North America is:",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Mount Everest",  "Mount Kilimanjaro", "Mount Elbrus"],
      correctAnswer: "Denali (Mount McKinley)",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "The largest country in the world by area is:",
      incorrectAnswers: ["China", "United States",  "Canada"],
      correctAnswer: "Russia",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "The largest continent in the world is:",
      incorrectAnswers: [ "Africa", "Europe", "North America"],
      correctAnswer: "Asia",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "The country that has the most number of time zones is:",
      incorrectAnswers: [ "United States", "China", "Australia"],
      correctAnswer: "Russia",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "The river that flows through Egypt is the:",
      incorrectAnswers: [ "Amazon River", "Yangtze River", "Mississippi River"],
      correctAnswer: "Nile River",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "The smallest country in the world is:",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Monaco", "San Marino",  "Liechtenstein"],
      correctAnswer: "Vatican City",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "The ocean that is the largest and deepest on Earth is the: ",
        incorrectAnswers: ["Atlantic Ocean", "Arctic Ocean",  "Indian Ocean"],
        correctAnswer: "Pacific Ocean",
      },
      
  ];

  export default data;